<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Job Quest Organizer Navigation</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string name="calendar">Calendar</string>
    <string name="list">Top Companies</string>
    <string name="companies">Companies</string>
    <string name="contacts">Contacts</string>
    <string name="applications">Applications</string>
    <string name="interviews">Interviews</string>

    <string-array name="motivation_array">
        <item>Motivation</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="time_array">
        <item>PM</item>
        <item>AM</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="getting_started">The purpose of Job Quest Organizer is to keep yourself organized
                during your job search process. In the menu, you will see a list of activities you
                can complete beginning with making a list of your Top Companies, all the way through
                keeping track of any Applications you have filled out and which you have received
                Interviews for. You can also set reminders to notify you of application deadlines,
                interview dates and times, or when to send follow-up emails.</string>
    <string name="top_companies">Start by making a list of your top 50 companies. At this point all
                you need to do is write down names. Once you get your 50, or as close as possible to 50.
                Then you check whether or not you can obtain a contact for that company, usually by
                checking on LinkedIn. The next step is to determine the your level of motivation for
                working at that company. The last step is to check the company website for available
                positions.</string>
    <string name="maintenance">After creating your list of top companies, you want to store information
                on those companies, any contacts you may have with those companies, whether or not you
                have applied to any open positions, and if you have received an interview for those applications.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
</resources>
